A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Projects, International Relations, RG 1.3, Series 155 FA388A
Rockefeller Archive Center
- International Relations, 1971-1989; 155
  - Harvard University: Energy Security, 1982 August (Box 57, Folder 629)
  - Harvard University: Energy Security, 1982 September-1984, 1986 April (Box 57, Folder 630)
  - Harvard University: Energy Security, 1986 December 23 (Box 57, Folder 631)
  - Harvard University: Energy Security, 1986 December 23 (Box 58, Folder 632)
  - Harvard University: Energy Security, 1986 December 23-1987 (Box 58, Folder 633)
  - John Harry Harwood, 1978-1981, 1984-1986 (Box 58, Folder 634)
  - Indian Council for Research on International Economic Relations: Monetary Conference, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 635)
  - Indian Council for Research on International Economic Relations: Monetary Conference, 1985-1986 (Box 58, Folder 636)
  - Indian Institute of Technology: Energy Consumption, 1978-1979 (Box 58, Folder 637)
  - Indian Institute of Technology: Energy Consumption, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 638)
  - Indian Institute of Technology: Energy Consumption, 1981-1983 (Box 58, Folder 639)
  - (489) – Institute for Black Research Trust: Research Fellow, 1985 March (Box 58, Folder 640)
  - (489) – Institute for Black Research Trust: Research Fellow, 1985 September-December (Box 58, Folder 641)
  - (489) – Institute for Black Research Trust: Research Fellow, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 642)
  - (489) – Institute for Black Research Trust: Research Fellow, 1988-1991 (Box 59, Folder 643)
  - Institute for East-West Security Studies: Middle East Conference, 1982-1983, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 644)
  - Institute for East-West Security Studies: Middle East Conference, 1982 December-1983 February (Box 59, Folder 645)
  - Institute for East-West Security Studies: Middle East Conference, 1983 March (Box 59, Folder 646)
  - Institute for East-West Security Studies: Middle East Conference, 1983 May-1984 (Box 59, Folder 647)
  - Institute for East-West Security Studies: Middle East Conference: Supplementary Material (I), 1984 (Box 59, Folder 648)
  - Institute for East-West Security Studies: Middle East Conference: Supplementary Material (II), 1985 June 14 (Box 59, Folder 649)
  - Institute for East-West Security Studies: Middle East Conference: Supplementary Material (III), 1985 June 14 (Box 59, Folder 650)
  - Institute for International Economics: Trade Policy Conference, 1982 February (Box 59, Folder 651)
  - Institute for International Economics: Trade Policy Conference, 1982 March-1983 (Box 59, Folder 652)
  - Institute for International Economics: Trade Policy Conference: Supplementary Material (I), 1982 June (Box 59, Folder 653)
  - Institute for International Economics: Trade Policy Conference: Supplementary Material (II), 1982 June (Box 60, Folder 654)
  - Institute for International Economics: Trade Policy Conference: Supplementary Material (III), 1982 June (Box 60, Folder 655)
  - Institute for International Economics: Trade Policy Conference: Supplementary Material (IV), 1982 June (Box 60, Folder 656)
  - Institute for International Economics: Trade Policy Conference: Supplementary Material (V), 1982 June (Box 60, Folder 657)
  - Institute for International Economics: Trade Policy Conference: Supplementary Material (VI), 1982 June (Box 60, Folder 658)
  - Institute for International Economics: Trade Policy Conference: Supplementary Material (VII), 1982 June (Box 60, Folder 659)
  - (489) – Institute of International Education: South African Education Evaluation, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 660)
  - (489) – Institute of International Education: South African Education Evaluation, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 661)
  - (489) – Institute of International Education: South African Education Evaluation, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 662)
  - (489) – Institute of International Education: South African Education Evaluation: Supplementary Material, 1981-1985 (Box 60, Folder 663)
  - Inter-American University: Caribbean Conference, 1982-1983, no date (Box 60, Folder 664)
  - Inter-American University: Caribbean Conference, 1984-1986, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 665)
  - Inter-American University: Caribbean Conference: Supplementary Material (I), 1983, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 666)
  - Inter-American University: Caribbean Conference: Supplementary Material (II), 1983 April (Box 61, Folder 667)
  - Inter-American University: Caribbean Conference: Supplementary Material (III), 1983 April (Box 61, Folder 668)
  - Inter-American University: Caribbean Conference: Supplementary Material (IV), 1983 April (Box 61, Folder 669)
  - Inter-American University: Caribbean Conference: Supplementary Material (V), 1983 April (Box 61, Folder 670)
  - Inter-American University: Caribbean Conference: Supplementary Material (VI): Working Papers, Nos. 1-3, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 671)
  - Inter-American University: Caribbean Conference: Supplementary Material (VII): Working Papers, Nos. 4-6, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 672)
  - Inter-American University: Caribbean Conference: Supplementary Material (VIII): Working Papers, Nos. 7-9, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 673)
  - Inter-American University: Caribbean Conference: Supplementary Material (IX): Working Papers, No. 14, no date (Box 61, Folder 674)
  - Inter-American University: Caribbean Conference: Supplementary Material (X): Working Papers, Nos. 24-26, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 675)
  - Inter-American University: Caribbean Conference: Supplementary Material (XI): Working Papers, Nos. 27-28, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 676)
  - (489) – Interdenominational African Ministers' Association of Southern Africa: Community Education, 1986-1990 (Box 61, Folder 677)
  - International Economic Studies Institute: Arms Control, 1982 May-August (Box 61, Folder 678)
  - International Economic Studies Institute: Arms Control, 1982 September-November (Box 61, Folder 679)
  - International Economic Studies Institute: Arms Control, 1983-1984 (Box 61, Folder 680)
  - International Law Association: State Immunity, 1978 February (Box 62, Folder 681)
  - International Law Association: State Immunity, 1978 April-1979 (Box 62, Folder 682)
  - International Law Association: State Immunity, 1981-1983 (Box 62, Folder 683)
  - International Peace Academy, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 684)
  - International Peace Academy, 1974 January-March (Box 62, Folder 685)
  - International Peace Academy, 1974 April-June (Box 62, Folder 686)
  - International Peace Academy, 1974 August-September (Box 62, Folder 687)
  - International Peace Academy, 1974 October-December (Box 62, Folder 688)
  - International Peace Academy, 1975 February-April (Box 62, Folder 689)
  - International Peace Academy, 1975 June-December (Box 62, Folder 690)
  - International Peace Academy, 1976 April-July (Box 62, Folder 691)
  - International Peace Academy, 1976 October-November (Box 62, Folder 692)
  - International Peace Academy, 1976 December (Box 63, Folder 693)
  - International Peace Academy, 1977 January (Box 63, Folder 694)
  - International Peace Academy, 1977 February-March (Box 63, Folder 695)
  - International Peace Academy, 1977 April-November (Box 63, Folder 696)
  - International Peace Academy, 1978 January-March (Box 63, Folder 697)
  - International Peace Academy, 1978 April-November (Box 63, Folder 698)
  - International Peace Academy, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 699)
  - International Peace Academy, 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 700)
  - International Peace Academy: Evaluation, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 701)
  - International Peace Academy: Supplementary Material (I), 1974, no date (Box 63, Folder 702)
  - International Peace Academy: Supplementary Material (II): "Peacekeeper's Handbook", Draft, Chapters 5-7, 1977 February (Box 63, Folder 703)
  - International Peace Academy: Supplementary Material (III): "Peacekeeper's Handbook", Draft, Chapters 10 and 13, 1977 February (Box 63, Folder 704)
  - International Peace Academy: Supplementary Material (IV): Peacekeeper's Handbook, Chapters I-V, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 705)
  - International Peace Academy: Supplementary Material (V): Peacekeeper's Handbook, Chapters VI-XI, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 706)
  - International Research Center for Energy and Economic Development: Oil Output Absorption, 1979 February-April (Box 64, Folder 707)
  - International Research Center for Energy and Economic Development: Oil Output Absorption, 1979 June-1982, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 708)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Supplementary Material: Asian Dialogue: Bangkok Symposium, 1978 September (Box 64, Folder 709)
    Related Materials
    Related material on the Japan Center for International Exchange may be found in FA209, Rockefeller Foundation records, Projects, RG 1.3-RG 1.8 (A76-A82), Subseries RG 1.7 (A81), Boxes 717 and 718, Folders 4798-4803
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Supplementary Material: Asian Dialogue: 2nd Odwara Symposium, 1979 March (Box 64, Folder 710)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Supplementary Material: Data Series, 1978 March (Box 64, Folder 711)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Supplementary Material: Europe-Japan Conference: 2nd Europe-Japan Conference, January 1977, 1977 March (Box 64, Folder 712)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Supplementary Material: Europe-Japan Conference: 3rd Europe-Japan Conference, October 20-21, 1977, 1977 October (Box 64, Folder 713)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Supplementary Material: Europe-Japan Conference: 4th Europe-Japan Conference, April 19-21, 1979, 1979 April (Box 64, Folder 714)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Supplementary Material: Rice Production Symposium: Tokyo Symposium on "Plan for Doubling Rice Production in Asia", 1978 November (Box 65, Folder 715)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Supplementary Material: Rice Production Symposium: Tokyo Symposium on "Plan for Doubling Rice Production in Asia", 1978 November (Box 65, Folder 716)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Supplementary Material: Survey Reports, 1977 April (Box 65, Folder 717)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Supplementary Material: Survey Reports: Journals in International Relations, 1978 March (Box 65, Folder 718)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Supplementary Material: Survey Reports: Journals in International Relations, Supplement, Volume I, 1978 March (Box 65, Folder 719)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Supplementary Material: Survey Reports: Journals in International Relations, Supplement, Volume II, 1978 March (Box 65, Folder 720)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Supplementary Material: Survey Reports: Philanthropy in Japan, 1978 March (Box 65, Folder 721)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Supplementary Material: Survey Reports: Research Institutions in Japan, 1978 March (Box 66, Folder 722)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Asian Program, 1983 June-November (Box 66, Folder 723)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Asian Program, 1983 December-1984 (Box 66, Folder 724)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Asian Program, 1985 April (Box 66, Folder 725)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Asian Program, 1985 July-December (Box 66, Folder 726)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Asian Program, 1986 January-February (Box 66, Folder 727)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Asian Program, 1986 March-December (Box 66, Folder 728)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Asian Program, 1987-1988 (Box 66, Folder 729)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Asian Program: Supplementary Material (I), 1985 December (Box 66, Folder 730)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Asian Program: Supplementary Material (II): JCIE Research Reports, 1986 October (Box 66, Folder 731)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Asian Program: Supplementary Material (III): JCIE Research Reports, 1986 October (Box 66, Folder 732)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Asian Program: Supplementary Material (IV): JCIE Research Reports, 1986 November (Box 67, Folder 733)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Asian Security, 1979-1981 (Box 67, Folder 734)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Asian Security, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 735)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Asian Security, 1983 November 1 (Box 67, Folder 736)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Asian Security, 1983 November 1 (Box 67, Folder 737)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Asian Security, 1983 November 1 (Box 67, Folder 738)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Asian Security, 1983 November 1-8 (Box 67, Folder 739)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Charles E. Morrison, 1980-1982 (Box 67, Folder 740)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange: Charles E. Morrison, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 741)
  - Johns Hopkins University: Atlantic Triangle Conference, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 742)
  - Johns Hopkins University: Atlantic Triangle Conference, 1982-1983, 1985-1986 (Box 67, Folder 743)
  - Johns Hopkins University: Atlantic Triangle Conference: Supplementary Material (I), 1981 May (Box 68, Folder 744)
  - Johns Hopkins University: Atlantic Triangle Conference: Supplementary Material (II), 1981 May (Box 68, Folder 745)
  - Johns Hopkins University: Atlantic Triangle Conference: Supplementary Material (III), 1981 June (Box 68, Folder 746)
  - Johns Hopkins University: Atlantic Triangle Conference: Supplementary Material (IV), 1981 June (Box 68, Folder 747)
  - Keystone Center for Continuing Education: Radioactive Waste Management Workshop, 1979 January-February (Box 68, Folder 748)
  - Keystone Center for Continuing Education: Radioactive Waste Management Workshop, 1979 March-1981 (Box 68, Folder 749)
  - Keystone Center for Continuing Education: Radioactive Waste Management Workshop, 1982 February (Box 68, Folder 750)
  - Keystone Center for Continuing Education: Radioactive Waste Management Workshop, 1980 October, 1981 March (Box 68, Folder 751)
  - Keystone Center for Continuing Education: Radioactive Waste Management Workshop: Supplementary Material (I): "Appendices to the...Reports to the Ford Foundation", Appendices A-D-3, 1982 February (Box 68, Folder 752)
  - Keystone Center for Continuing Education: Radioactive Waste Management Workshop: Supplementary Material (II): "Appendices to the...Reports to the Ford Foundation", Appendix D-4, 1982 February (Box 68, Folder 753)
  - Keystone Center for Continuing Education: Radioactive Waste Management Workshop: Supplementary Material (III): "Appendices to the...Reports to the Ford Foundation", Appendices D-5-D-7, 1982 February (Box 68, Folder 754)
  - Keystone Center for Continuing Education: Radioactive Waste Management Workshop: Supplementary Material (IV): "Appendices to the...Reports to the Ford Foundation", Appendices D-8-F, 1982 February (Box 68, Folder 755)
  - Korea University: Korean-Asian Relations, 1982 March-July (Box 69, Folder 756)
  - Korea University: Korean-Asian Relations, 1982 August-1983, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 757)
  - Lawyers' Committee for Civil Rights Under Law: Apartheid Conference, 1978 February-May (Box 69, Folder 758)
  - Lawyers' Committee for Civil Rights Under Law: Apartheid Conference, 1978 July (Box 69, Folder 759)
  - Lawyers' Committee for Civil Rights Under Law: Apartheid Conference, 1978 August-1980 (Box 69, Folder 760)
  - Lawyers' Committee for Civil Rights Under Law: Apartheid Conference, 1981, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 761)
  - Lawyers' Committee for Civil Rights Under Law: Apartheid Conference: Evaluation, 1980-1982 (Box 69, Folder 762)
  - League of Women Voters Education Fund: National Security, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 763)
  - League of Women Voters Education Fund: National Security, 1983 (Box 69, Folder 764)
  - League of Women Voters Education Fund: National Security, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 765)
    - "National Security: Not for Experts Only" - League of Women Voters Education Fund, 2016:FA388A:001; Enclosure in Alice Hughey (League of Women Voters Education Fund) letter of May 7, 1986, to John Stremlau (Box 69)
  - League of Women Voters Education Fund: National Security, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 766)
  - League of Women Voters Education Fund: National Security: Supplementary Material, 1980, 1982-1984 (Box 69, Folder 767)
  - (489) – Legal Resources Trust: Advice Office, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 768)
  - (489) – Legal Resources Trust: Advice Office, 1983 (Box 70, Folder 769)
  - (489) – Legal Resources Trust: Advice Office, 1984-1985, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 770)
  - (489) – Legal Resources Trust: Advice Office: Supplementary Material (I), 1980-1982 (Box 70, Folder 771)
  - (489) – Legal Resources Trust: Advice Office: Supplementary Material (II), 1980-1982 (Box 70, Folder 772)
  - (489) – Legal Resources Trust: Port Elizabeth Office, 1985-1986 (Box 70, Folder 773)
  - (489) – Legal Resources Trust: Port Elizabeth Office, 1987, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 774)
  - Chi-Yuan Liang, 1978-1980 (Box 70, Folder 775)
  - Chi-Yuan Liang: Supplementary Material, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 776)
  - Fernando Reyes Manibog, 1978-1979 (Box 70, Folder 777)
  - Fernando Reyes Manibog, 1980-1982 (Box 70, Folder 778)
  - Fernando Reyes Manibog: "A Rural Energy Survey and Cost-Effectiveness Analysis of Renewable Energy Technologies for a Philippine Island Community", pp. 1-83, 1984 March (Box 70, Folder 779)
  - Fernando Reyes Manibog: "A Rural Energy Survey and Cost-Effectiveness Analysis of Renewable Energy Technologies for a Philippine Island Community", pp. 84-183, 1984 March (Box 71, Folder 780)
  - Fernando Reyes Manibog: "A Rural Energy Survey and Cost-Effectiveness Analysis of Renewable Energy Technologies for a Philippine Island Community", pp. 184-240, 1984 March (Box 71, Folder 781)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: Energy and Economy in Developing Countries, 1982-1984 (Box 71, Folder 782)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: U. S.-Japanese Nuclear Energy Workshop, 1979-1982 (Box 71, Folder 783)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 784)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study, 1978 April-August (Box 71, Folder 785)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study, 1978 September-December (Box 71, Folder 786)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 787)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study, 1980 January (Box 71, Folder 788)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study, 1980 March 4-12 (Box 71, Folder 789)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study, 1980 March 12 (Box 71, Folder 790)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study, 1980 March 20-April (Box 71, Folder 791)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study, 1980 May-1981 (Box 72, Folder 792)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (I): Draft, "Proposed Coal Trade Study", Exhibit 1-Exhibit 5, Annex B, 1978 April (Box 72, Folder 793)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (II): Draft, "Proposed Coal Trade Study", Exhibit 5, Annexes C-F, 1978 April (Box 72, Folder 794)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (III), 1978 May (Box 72, Folder 795)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (IV), 1978 June-September (Box 72, Folder 796)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (V): Summary Report, Aspen Meetings, October 31, 1978, Volume 1, 1978 October (Box 72, Folder 797)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (VI): Summary Report, Aspen Meetings, October 31, 1978, Volume 2, pp. 1-118, 1978 October (Box 72, Folder 798)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (VII): Summary Report, Aspen Meetings, October 31, 1978, Volume 2, pp. 119-227, 1978 October (Box 72, Folder 799)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (VIII), 1978 (Box 72, Folder 800)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (IX), 1978 December (Box 72, Folder 801)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (X): "Summary Report, St. Paul Associates' Meeting, February 25-March 3, 1979", Volume I, 1979 March (Box 72, Folder 802)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (XI): "Summary Report, St. Paul Associates' Meeting, February 25-March 3, 1979", Volume 2, pp. 1-131, 1979 March (Box 72, Folder 803)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (XII): "Summary Report, St. Paul Associates' Meeting, February 25-March 3, 1979", Volume 2, pp. 132-333, 1979 March (Box 73, Folder 804)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (XIII), 1979 April (Box 73, Folder 805)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (XIV): "Summary Report, Aarhus Meeting, June 24-30, 1979", July 10, 1979, Volume 1 (Box 73, Folder 806)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (XV): "WOCO National Reports, Aarhus Participants' Meeting, June 24-27, 1979", Volume 1, pp. 1-143, 1979 July (Box 73, Folder 807)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (XVI): "WOCO National Reports, Aarhus Participants' Meeting, June 24-27, 1979", Volume 1, pp. 144-302, 1979 July (Box 73, Folder 808)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (XVII): "WOCO National Reports", Aarhus Meetings, June 24-30, 1979, Volume 2, pp. 1-206, 1979 July (Box 73, Folder 809)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (XVIII): "WOCO National Reports", Aarhus Meetings, June 24-30, 1979, Volume 2, pp. 207-366, 1979 July (Box 73, Folder 810)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (XIX): "WOCO National Reports", Aarhus Meetings, June 24-30, 1979, Volume 2, pp. 367-528, 1979 July (Box 73, Folder 811)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (XX), 1979 August (Box 73, Folder 812)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (XXI), 1979 September 12 (Box 73, Folder 813)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (XXII), 1979 September 20 (Box 74, Folder 814)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (XXIII): Prototype of WOCOL Final Report, Volume 2, Part I, pp. 1-166, 1979 September 20 (Box 74, Folder 815)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (XXIV): Prototype of WOCOL Final Report, Volume 2, Part I, pp. 167-378, 1979 September 20 (Box 74, Folder 816)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (XXV): Prototype of WOCOL Final Report, Volume 2, Part I, pp. 379-522, 1979 September 20 (Box 74, Folder 817)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (XXVI): Prototype of WOCOL Final Report, Volume 2, Part 2, 1979 September 20 (Box 74, Folder 818)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (XXVII), 1979 October-November (Box 74, Folder 819)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (XXVIII), 1980 March-May (Box 74, Folder 820)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (XXIX): "World Press Reception of the WOCOL Final Report", Australia-Germany, 1980 June (Box 74, Folder 821)